exe. So basically we already discussed before. The Windows machines will be saving logs
to one of the folder, right? It will be saving each and every logs to unfold. The logs
will be like security logs. When you are logging into the machine, it will be the logs will
be logged there and every application logs and everything will be there, right? So it will be
dependent on the WV, we need to fold up. So now you can just come to the bottom. You can see
there is a security logs that was an L20, 484, 485 KB. So now if I open the security log,
yeah. So if I open the security logs, so you can see a lot of security, you can see a lot
of information about the security. So when I will log into the machine, when I log, when I did
a shut-on the machine, the each and everything will be logged, right? So this Windows
you till, where you till, we will clear, we can able to clear all the logs, okay, all the logs from the
session. So why we need to, why the detector need to clear the logs from the logs from the
director, okay? So I already mentioned those, so this logs is evidence, okay? So evidence of
investigation, receiver, a booty or if for a threat analyst, if you are doing a foreign six or
anything, so you need some logs, right? You need some evidence to investigate if there is no
evidence, you can't able to investigate what's happened inside the machine, okay? So the threat
actors will, or hackers, they will delete this log, they will, they will, they will do clearing
these logs. So if the threat actors cleared this log, so you, you do not have any data to
investigate, okay? So probably you are a cooler, so you don't know what happened inside the
machine, okay? So we can do this by using one of the log bats, w, v, t, u, t, i, l, dot exe, so this is
the executable and you need to give the c, l, c, l means clear. So now you can give the security,
a, c, c, u, r, i, t, y, sorry. So let's refresh this and see, so now you can see there's
only one log, there's only one even tried, so the unit was 110 to even tidy, log clear, there's
a log clear even tidy, the, even tidy was 110 to someone, because we, we cleared that log, okay?
You can see now, we have cleared their logs and the, even tidy is 110 to that it has been logged and
this user, this is the user, he cleared the log, the audit log was cleared, okay? So this was used to
by many hackers and many threat actors, especially the ransomware threat actors, because they need to
delete all the evidence from the machines, so they will be doing this kind of malicious things
by using the tutil.ex, okay? So let's stop off this video and we'll continue our discussion in our
next video. See you guys, bye-bye.